# Sally R. Perez

seattlesally1@gmail.com | (206) 371-2958 Seattle, WA https://www.linkedin.com/in/sallyrperez/ https://github.com/SeattleSal

#### **SUMMARY**

Web developer interested in positions including Full Stack Web Developer that use my problem-solving mindset to continuously learn new skills at a customer focused company. Recently completed the Certificate in Full Stack Web Development from University of Washington and have skills in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and a degree in Computer Science. 15+ years as a Technology Auditor at retail (Starbucks, Nordstrom) and technology companies (Amazon). Attracted to the continuous learning aspect of IT and Technology Auditing, every audit project was a chance to learn about a new product, process and/or technology. Ready to move beyond the focus on analysis to creating valuable solutions.

### **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, MySQL, NodeJS, ReactJS
- Communication, team player, curious, problem solver

#### **PROJECTS PORTFOLIO**

Online portfolio: https://seattlesal.github.io/Portfolio/

- <u>Feast with Friends</u> Application to find restaurants based on the user and user friends dietary restrictions. Created with JavaScript, NodeJS and Bootstrap and uses 3P API.
- <u>Trail Chasers</u> Application to discovery trails based on location and result in trail information, weather and directions to trail. Created with JavaScript and Bulma and uses 3P APIs.
- <u>Burgers</u> Application to capture user's list of burgers to be eaten and already eaten. Created with JavaScript, NodeJS and Bootstrap.
- <u>Weather Dashboard</u> Application to display weather details for given location. Created with JavaScript and CSS and uses 3P API for weather.
- <u>Wizard of Oz Quiz</u> Quiz application with questions about the Wizard of Oz book series. Created with JavaScript and CSS.

### **DEGREES AND CERTIFICATIONS**

- Full Stack Web Development Certificate, University of Washington, March 2021
- Certified Information Systems Auditor (CISA), 09/2007 12/2020
- Project Management Professional (PMP), 01/2012 02/2018
- Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO), 09/2015 09/2017
- Data and Internet Security Certificate, University of Washington Extension Program, 2006
- Bachelor's in Computer Science, Arizona State University, Graduated Magna Cum Laude, 2003

## **EXPERIENCE**

Amazon, Seattle, WA

Senior Manager Tech Audit | May 2019 - March 2020

Tech Audit Manager | January 2017 - May 2019

- Managed audit portfolio for Devices, Alexa and Digital Content spaces including Music, Video and Studios. Managed and provided oversight for a team of four.
- Performed end-to-end audit projects over Devices, Alexa, Music, Advertising and InfoSec.
   Executed test plans over Amazon Web Services (AWS) Identity and Access Management and S3 services.
- Streamlined and built IT General Controls test work programs and training for Internal Audit team.

Outerwall, Bellevue, WA

Senior IT Audit Manager | November 2015 - October 2016

- Begin establishment of in house IT Audit function that was formerly outsourced.
- Supported SOX IT work and executed risk based technology audits.
- Created quality assurance improvement program for Internal Audit activities.

# Sally R. Perez

Nordstrom, Seattle, WA

IT Audit Principal | April 2013 – November 2015

- Planned and executed two year Privacy audit program based on Generally Accepted Privacy Principles. Identified gaps and improvement areas in handling of third party vendors.
- Planned and executed IT risk assessment and audits over Nordstrom Federal Savings Bank (NFSB) technology environment incorporating guidance from FFIEC IT Handbooks.
- Co-led professional practices initiatives such as continuous process improvement including use of kaizens, benchmarking for best practices and improving communication mechanisms.

Starbucks Coffee Company, Seattle, WA Audit Manager | January 2012 – March 2013 IT Audit Project Manager | January 2011 – January 2012 Senior IT Auditor | May 2006 – January 2011

- Provided support and guidance for four direct reports and other team members on projects including compliance audits, operational/financial/IT audits and risk assessments.
- Coordinated and managed reviews in multiple international licensed and joint-venture markets.
- Created system implementation controls self-assessment checklist to proactively address
  upcoming system implementation reviews, scope future audits and communicate risks with IT
  stakeholders.
- Led the planning, execution and coordination of a pre-implementation audit review of the largest software implementation in the history of Starbucks at the time. Communicated issues and addressed concerns to external audit team and created communication for executives including the CIO, CFO and Audit Committee.
- Acted as subject matter expert of TeamMate audit software for Internal Audit department.
   Provided guidance on technical issues and troubleshooting, acted as liaison with IT to roll out installation of new modules, functionality setting and upgrades.

## Boeing, Renton, WA

IT Security Advisor | July 2005 - April 2006

- Coordinated activities to ensure compliance to export regulations in support of the Multi-Maritime Aircraft (MMA) project including defining scope and identifying compliance solutions. Provided deliverables including legal, export, program managers and application owners.
- Provided focused security policy internal customer support by creating solutions to meet compliance.

Boeing, Multiple locations (WA, CO, AZ)

Information Technology Generalist | July 2003 – July 2005

- Six four month rotations through various functions, teams and locations:
  - o IT Audit review with a focus on information security at Jeppesen subsidiary.
  - o Code migration and security access services for defense location.
  - o Change management for architecture integration.
  - o Program and change management for IT Governance program.
  - o Functional analyst for internal engineer software.
  - o Process workflows and training for IT Architecture team.